# BRAYAN MEJIA CUENCA

(C) 5109412942 | Learnwithbrayan@gmail.com | https://github.com/Mejiabrayan

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Marketing Assistant with a demonstrated history of working in the non-profit organization management industry. Skilled in Web Design, Spanish Translation, HTML, Adobe Photoshop, and Leadership. Strong marketing professional with aiming for his Associate's degree focused on Marketing and Sales at Berkeley City College.

# SKILLS

- Bilingual: English, Spanish & Hebrew
- Written and verbal communication Skills
- Interpersonal Skills
- Customer Service
- Preparing, editing letters, reports, memos, and emails
- Administrative and clerical tasks (such as scanning or printing)
- Familiarity with: Word, Excel, Google Docs & Powerpoint
- Computer Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node
- Adobe Creative Suite tools: Photoshop and Sketch

## **WORK HISTORY**

JUNE 2019-SEPTEMBER 2019

Marketing Assistant Intern | Downtown Berkeley Association | Berkeley, CA

- Conducted project research on City trash bins to help improve, and relocate over 20+ trash bins resulting in reduced waste
- Increased production by 40% by proofreading and editing marketing materials
- Assisted with coordinating events such as Berkeley Sunday Streets and BAMPFA live outdoor movie screenings by arranging seating, booths and handing out flyers
- Increased production by 45% by creating and maintaining website and database including production and scheduling product life cycle tracking

APRIL 2019-JULY 2019

Digital Communications Intern | Piikup | Oakland, CA

Assisted with curating email marketing content

- Subscribed, created and segmented new audience list which helped boost list of subscribers by 3% via Mailchimp
- Track email stats based on audience click rate and performance to keep up with email engagement
- Participated in Job Fairs; helped with recruiting potential employees
- Organized database information into a spreadsheet and imported them into bulk CSV files
- Assisted with writing, editing and publishing blogs on the company's website

#### JANUARY 2019-APRIL 2019

#### Hack The Hood Bootcamp | Oakland, CA

- Designed and implemented Websites for Small Business Clients using HTML and CSS, including UX/UI
- Coordinated consultations with clients to discuss their needs and vision of their business
- Participated in Professional Development Workshops to build strong portfolios and resumes
- Attended Conferences to build up networking skills

#### JUNE 2017-AUGUST 2017

#### Civic Engagement Pilgrimage Internship | Kent, Washington

- Facilitating small group listening Meetings at large events at over 30 civic forums
- Developed an understanding of the role of civics, ethics, values, community engagement in Education used them to teach, present, and mentor effectively
- Co-wrote a new disciplinary system for public High schools in Kent Washington
- Critically analyze race, indifference, and hatred as part of a research project
- Served as a mentor and leader to High school students while working to build the communities within Washington
- Practiced ethical leadership, citizenship, and social responsibility

## **EDUCATION**

2019

Associate of Arts: Sales & Marketing

Berkeley City College, located in Berkeley, CA

2016

Camp Woolman, Nevada City, CA

Educational semester abroad program that weaves together spirituality, peace, sustainability, and social action. Our lives and work embody a vision for peace and justice achieved through learning and service. Located in Nevada City, California.

References available upon request.